

+977 9840 135 185
iambishistha@gmail.com
thevisualx.design
LinkedIn | Dribbble | Instagram

A Product Designer driven by user-centric outcomes.

I started as a Graphic Designer blending creativity and aesthetics into everyday work but later transitioned into a product realm focusing on user-centric research and design. Being a self-taught designer, I have a broad discipline of design domains from product, graphic, and motion to video editing.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCES

Senior Product Designer, Naamche

Dec 2024 - Present • Dillibazar, Kathmandu

Helping build the world's first commission-free Al homebuying platform

Product Designer, Leapfrog Technology

Aug 2022 - Dec 2024 • Dillibazar, Kathmandu

US-based Retail Analytics Software

Helped redesign the product to meet new business goals

Laudio | US-based Healthcare Product

Helped build, improve and redesign a system to improve workforce management

Collaborated in setting up a Design System based on Design Tokens to scale design and better dev/design collaboration

Vyaguta | In-house ERP Product

Built an in-house OKR platform and worked on integrating and improving multiple features

Others | UI/UX

Facilitated sessions on Design Thinking and collaborated on multiple Standard Operating Procedures (SOP) documents

Graphic Designer, Leapfrog Technology

Aug 2020 - Jul 2022 • Dillibazar, Kathmandu

Helped multiple US-based clients with marketing collaterals like posters and videos

Part of the team to initiate, lead and mentor the Leapfrog Student Partnership Program and Batch I students

Graphic Designer, Branding Bee

Aug 2019 - Jun 2020 • Baluwatar, Kathmandu

Worked with various clients like $\underline{\text{MediaHub}}\,^{\, {\sc z}}$ and $\underline{\text{Tesla AC}}\,^{\, {\sc z}}$ for graphic needs

View all on LinkedIn [↗]

SKILLS

Industry Knowledge

Product Design, Product Thinking, User-centered Design, UX Research, Design Thinking, Double Diamond, Interaction Design, Prototyping, Design System, Graphic Design, Brand Identity Design, Digital Painting, Image Editing & Manipulation, Motion Graphics, Video Editing, HTML, CSS

Tools

Figma/FigJam, Mixpanel, Jira, Google Suite Apps, Adobe CC Apps, Miro, Notion, Monday, Productboard

Others

Squarespace, GitHub, WordPress, Mailerlite, Team Player, Mentorship

RELEVANT CERTIFICATIONS

Enterprise Design Thinking Practitioner

IBM • Jul 2024 7

Google Certified UX Designer

Coursera • Jun 2023 7

EDUCATION

Anna University

Bachelor in Computer Science & Engineering 2014 - 2018

LANGUAGES

Nepali (Native) English (Professional) Newari (Native) Hindi (Limited)